You'll also notice in the sample code that we
have lines that call log.e, which log error messages. With
the adb command line tool and with the device plugged
in, you can type adb logcat to see the debug
and error messages that are being printed to the logcat.
For more details on the logcat options, see the link
below. Another way to view the logs, is to use
Android Studio. If you click on the Screen Android button,
it launches the Android Device Monitor. Which includes the
DDMS tool that Rado mentioned earlier. Then click on a
device and you can see that our app here, is
a running process. If you click on the LogCat tab,
then you all these log messages here, which is what
we saw with adb logcat. Now try viewing the logs
yourself with either of those methods. If you do both,
then you get brownie points. Check this box to proceed.